A Guide to the Virginia Daughters of the American Revolution Records, 1947
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Virginia Daughters of the American Revolution, 1947
The Library of Virginia
22676
.225 cu. ft. and 1 box
Virginia Daughters of the American Revolution
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Mrs. John H. Hoskins, State Chair, Genealogical Records Committee, Daughters of the American Revolution, 116 Linden Avenue, Lynchburg, Virginia.
Scope and Content
Records, 1947 of the Virginia Daughters of the American Revolution consisting of Bible records and genealogical notes, biographies, cemetery records, epitaphs, judicial records, resolves, wills, and other papers. Records are copies made of original sources by various chapters of the Virginia Daughters of the American Revolution.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: Bible Records and Genealogical Notes
Series II: Cemetery Records
Series III: Wills
Series IV: Miscellaneous Files
Contents List
- Series I: Bible Records and Genealogical Notes., Extent: 29 folders. (Folder 1-29)
  - Bates family. (Folder 1)
  - Blanton family. (Folder 2)
  - Boston family. (Folder 3)
  - Coleman family. (Folder 4)
  - Cowherd family. (Folder 5)
  - Cruikshank family. (Folder 6)
  - Douglass family. (Folder 7)
  - DuVal family. (Folder 8)
  - Goggin and Gardner families. (Folder 9)
  - Gray family (see also Hayman). (Folder 10)
  - Green family. (Folder 11)
  - Gregory family. (Folder 12)
  - Hayman family (see also Gray). (Folder 13)
  - Heaton family (see also Offley). (Folder 14)
  - Henry family. (Folder 15)
  - Myers family. (Folder 16)
  - Offley family (see also Heaton). (Folder 17)
  - Purvis family. (Folder 18)
  - Roane family. (Folder 19)
  - Rorer family. (Folder 20)
  - Sandidge family. (Folder 21)
  - Simpson-Selecman families. (Folder 22)
  - Staples family. (Folder 23)
  - Talbot family. (Folder 24)
  - Timberlake family. (Folder 25)
  - Walker family. (Folder 26)
  - Waugh-Willis family. (Folder 27)
  - Wax family. (Folder 28)
  - Webb family. (Folder 29)
- Series II: Cemetery Records., Extent: 4 folders. (Folder 30-33)
  - Alexandria and Fairfax County. (Folder 30)
  - Culpeper County. (Folder 31)
  - Hanover and Stafford Counties. (Folder 32)
  - Pulaski County. (Folder 33)
- Series III: Wills., Extent: 6 folders. (Folder 34-39)
  - Joseph Force. (Folder 34)
  - Jacob Kent. (Folder 35)
  - Peter Miller. (Folder 36)
  - William Waters. (Folder 37)
  - Henry Wax (Waches). (Folder 38)
  - Wilson Woodroof. (Folder 39)
- Series IV: Miscellaneous Files., Extent: 11 boxes. (Folder 40-50)
  - Individuals: Boyd J. Bolling. (Folder 40)
  - Individuals: Thomas Farley, Sr. (Folder 41)
  - William McIntosh. (Folder 42)
  - Judicial Records: Bedford County orders of the court abstracts (Talbot family), 1753-1784. (Folder 43)
  - Judicial Records: King George County court orders abstracts (Monteith et Uxor to Owens, 1737. (Folder 44)
  - Judicial Records: Northampton County minute books abstracts, 1771-1784. (Folder 45)
  - County Records: Fairfax County Resolves, 1769. (Folder 46)
  - County Records: Scott County marriages, 1846-1847. (Folder 47)
  - Pensions: List of pensioners and applicants for pensions in Franklin County, Virginia, and war claims allowed in Greenbrier County, (West) Virginia. (Folder 48)
  - Pensions: Extracts from report of Revolutionary Claims (35th Congress)--John Paulding, Isaac Van Wert, and David Williams. (Folder 49)
  - Records of the Thomas Nelson Chapter (Arlington, Virginia), containing information on the Ball, Benton, Bridges, Carter, Catlin, Gray, Gwinn, Snoddy, Threlkeld, and Tracy families; the Ball and Gray family homes of Eastwood, Sherwood Forest, and Traveler's Rest; Carter family home of Corotoman; and epitaphs from Stafford County. (Folder 50)